{
    "subject": "Mary_Lee_Woods",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Conway_Berners-Lee",
    "human_readable": "Mary Lee Woods is married to Conway Berners-Lee.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9489504098892212,
            "question": "Who is Mary Lee Woods married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9357207417488098,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Mary Lee Woods and Conway Berners-Lee?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9260644912719727,
            "question": "Is Conway Berners-Lee married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9053329825401306,
            "question": "Who are Mary Lee Woods and Conway Berners-Lee?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8794089555740356,
            "question": "Name the spouse of Conway Berners-Lee."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8683476448059082,
            "question": "Who is Mary Lee Woods' husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8506309986114502,
            "question": "Is Mary Lee Woods related to Tim Berners-Lee?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8438808917999268,
            "question": "To whom is Mary Lee Woods connected?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7757200002670288,
            "question": "What is the name of Conway Berners-Lee's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7620623111724854,
            "question": "What is the marital status of Conway Berners-Lee?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mary Lee Woods is married to Conway Berners-Lee.",
            "html": "yago_9087_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Conway Berners-Lee's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_9087_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To whom is Mary Lee Woods connected?",
            "html": "yago_9087_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Mary Lee Woods related to Tim Berners-Lee?",
            "html": "yago_9087_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9087_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9087_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9087_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9087_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9087_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9087_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9087_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9087_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9087_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9087_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Mary Lee Woods was married to Conway-Berners Lee, which supports the statement that Mary Lee Woods is married to Conway Berners-Lee."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}